jobs.com.sg 2018-12-20

# Jobs.com.sg

**Privacy Statement**

By entering this Website, you (“Users”) agree to abide to the following privacy policy ("Policy") governing the use of RJ Media Pte. Ltd. (Company Registration Number: [200719544R]) (“Publisher”) websites comprising of www.jobs.com.sg and other websites owned by RJ Media Pte Ltd (“Websites”).If you do not accept these terms and conditions and privacy policy, you do not have the right to access these Websites and are requested to leave the Websites immediately. 

The Publisher may from time to time amend or vary this Policy by posting the revised Policy on these Websites. The continued use of the Websites after the amendment of this Policy will be deemed to be acceptance of the amended Policy by Users. However, if you do not agree with the amended Policy, Users are requested to leave the Websites immediately. 

If Users have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, Users can contact HeadHunt’s Helpdesk at helpdesk@headhunt.com.sg. 

The Publisher respects the privacy of the personal information and data of its users and will ensure compliance by its staff to the strictest standards of security and confidentiality in respect of all personal information and data submitted by users via the Websites and the Publisher will not, subject to the terms herein, release such information to anyone without the prior consent of the relevant Users. 

Users are strongly recommended to read this privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”) carefully to have an understanding of the Publisher’s policy and practices with regard to the treatment of personal information and data provided by Users on the Websites. This Privacy Statement is applicable to both registered and unregistered Users, and the terms herein may be updated, revised, varied and/or amended from time to time as the Publisher may deem necessary and/or appropriate. 

By registering for or using the services/Websites, or by clicking the ‘Register’ button, Users: 

(a) consent to the Publisher and its Websites collecting, using, disclosing and/or processing User’s personal data for the purposes as described below; 

(b) consent to the Publisher and its Websites disclosing Users’ personal data to the Publisher’s third party service providers or agents (whether within or outside Singapore) for the purposes as described below. 

If Users have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, they should contact the Publisher, whose contact details are set out below. 

**Preamble**

The Websites are a web-based executive job advertising service that enables Users to search for job openings ("Job Seekers") by accessing job advertisements ("Adverts") placed by and/or aggregated from companies, government, non-profit organisations and recruitment agencies ("Advertiser") and to apply for positions contained within those Adverts. 

**Purpose of Collection and Use of Personal Data**

In the course of using the Site, Users may disclose or be asked to provide personal information and/or data. In order to have the benefit of and enjoy various services offered by the Websites, it may be necessary for Users to provide the Publisher with their personal information and/or data. Although Users are not obliged to provide the information and/or data as requested on the Websites, the Publisher will not be able to render certain services on the Websites in the event that Users fail to do so. 

The Publisher’s purposes for collecting and using the information and data on the Websites include but not limited to the following: 

(a) for the daily operation of the services provided to Users; 

(b) to assist Job Seekers to find appropriate employment with Employers and to assist Employers to assess the suitability of candidates for a job vacancy for a wide spectrum of jobs an industries; 

(c) to provide Users with various services offered by the Websites and newsletters, information on job openings and promotional and marketing materials (for further details, please refer to section headed "Subscription of Newsletter/Promotional Materials/Marketing Materials" below); 

(d) to handle and follow up on enquiries, requests and complaints from Users; 

(e) to contact Users regarding administrative notices and communications relevant to his/her use of the Websites and to respond to Users’ inquiries or requests; 

(f) to assist the Publisher with developments for future marketing and promoting purposes or other internal purposes 

(g) to identify Users who have viewed the Information posted on the Websites; 

(h) to identify Users who have enjoyed their benefits as members of the Websites by receiving and using marketing promotional materials; 

(i) to facilitate the Publisher and/or its affiliates to use the Users' personal data for the purposes relating to the provision of services offered by the Publisher and marketing services and/or special event of the Publisher and/or its affiliates; 

(j) to obtain statistics about Users to analyse usage of the Websites in order to help its further development; and 

(k) for purposes other than the above mentioned which are related to the Publisher and/or its affiliates’ provision of their product and/or services. 

Before using the Websites or disclosing any information or data on the Websites, Users under the age of 18 should seek prior consent from a person with parental responsibility for him/her, e.g. parent or guardian, who may contact the Publisher whose contact details are set out under the section headed “Enquiries” for registering the User as member of the Websites. 

The Publisher strives to only collect personal data which are necessary and adequate but not excessive in relation to the purposes set out hereinabove. 

If the Publisher requires the use of your personal data for a purpose other than those set out hereinabove, we will request your prescribed consent to the same. If you are a minor, the prescribed consent should be given by your parent or guardian. 

**Collection of Personal Data**

The Publisher may collect personal information and/or data about a User, such as his/her name, log-in ID and password, address, email address, phone number, age, gender, date of birth, country of residence, nationality, education level and work experience that is/are not otherwise publicly available. Occasionally, the Publisher may also collect additional personal information and/or data from a User in connection with contests, surveys, or special offers. 

Only duly authorised staff of the Publisher will be permitted to access Users’ personal information and data, and the Publisher shall not release such personal information and data to any third parties save and except in the circumstances listed under the section headed “Disclosure or Transfer of Data” below. 

**Disclosure or Transfer of Data**

The Publisher agrees to take all practicable steps to keep all personal information and data of Users confidential and/or undisclosed, subject to the following. 

Generally speaking, the Publisher will only disclose and/or transfer Users’ personal information and/or data to the Publisher’s personnel and staff for the purpose of providing services to Users and corporate clients (including but not limited to Advertisers and Employers) of the Publisher who have made specific requests for such information and/or data with Users’ prior consent. However, the Publisher may disclose and/or transfer such information and/or data to third parties under the following circumstances: 

(a) where the information and/or data is disclosed and/or transferred to any third party suppliers or external service providers who have been duly authorised by the Publisher to use such information and/or data and who will facilitate the services on the Websites, under a duty of confidentiality; 

(b) where the information and/or data is disclosed and/or transferred to any agents, affiliates or associates of the Publisher who have been duly authorised by the Publisher to use such information and/or data; 

(c) where permitted under the “Terms and Conditions” 

(d) where the Publisher needs to protect and defend its rights and property; 

(e) where the Publisher considers necessary to do so in order to comply with the applicable laws and regulations, including without limitation compliance with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the Websites; 

(f) where the Publisher deems necessary in order to deliver the products and services that we offer and cultivate a positive user experience; and/or 

(g) where the Publisher deems necessary in order to maintain and/or improve the services on the Websites. 

Personal data collected via the Websites may be transferred, stored and processed in any country in which the Publisher or its affiliates operate. By using the Websites, Users are deemed to have agreed to, consented to and authorised the Publisher to disclose and/or transfer their personal information and data under the circumstances stated above, as well as to any transfer of information (including the Information) outside of the Users’ country. 

**Subscription of Newsletter/Promotional Materials/Marketing Materials**

The Publisher and its affiliates may from time to time send to members and Users of the Websites newsletters, information on job openings, and marketing materials based on the personal information and data that they have provided to the Publisher. The Publisher may use Users' data in direct marketing and the Publisher requires the Users' consent (which includes an indication of no objection) for that purpose. In this connection, please note that: 

(a) the name, log-in ID and password, contact details, age, gender, date of birth, country of residence, nationality, education level and work experience of Users held by the Publisher from time to time may be used by the Publisher and/or its authorised personnel or staff in direct marketing; 

(b) the above products, services and subjects may be provided or (in the case of donations and contributions) solicited by the Publisher and/or; 

i. The Publisher’s affiliates; 

ii. third party service providers providing the products, services and subjects listed in paragraph (b) above; and 

iii. charitable or non-profit making organisations; 

(c) in addition to marketing the above services, products, and subject itself, the Publisher also intends to provide the data described in paragraph (a) above to all or any of the persons described in paragraph (c) above for use by them in marketing those services, products and subjects, and the Publisher requires the Users' written consent (which includes an indication of no objection) for that purpose; and 

In this regard, Users may choose to sign up or unsubscribe for such materials by logging into their Websites account and changing their My Alert notifications, or clicking on the automatic link appearing in each newsletter/message or contact the Publisher, whose contact details are set out under the section headed “Enquiries”. 

**Access to or request for correction of data**

Any User is entitled to request access to or make amendments to his/her own personal information and data kept with the Publisher by contacting the Publisher at whose contact details are set out under the section headed “Enquiries”. Subject to the paragraph below, User may alternatively edit, amend or delete his/her personal information and data at any time by logging into the “My Alerts” section of the Site. 

The Publisher will also endeavour to provide requested information quickly but reserves the rights to charge the User a reasonable fee for doing so. 

**Cookies and Log Files**

The Publisher does not collect any personally identifiable information from any Users whilst they visit and browse the Site. When Users access the Websites, the Publisher records their visits only and does not collect their personal information or data. The Website’s server software will also record the domain name, server, address and track the pages Users visit and store such information in “cookies”, and gather and store information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data, in log files. All these are done without the Users being aware that they are occurring. 

Users can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but users can modify their individual browser settings to decline cookies if they prefer. However, Users should note that disabling cookies on their browser may prevent them from taking full advantage of the website. 

The Publisher does not link the information and data automatically collected in the above manner to any personally identifiable information. The Publisher generally uses such automatically collected information and data to estimate the audience size of the Websites, gauge the popularity of various parts of the Websites, track Users’ movements and number of entries in the Publisher’s promotional activities and special events, measure Users’ traffic patterns and administer the Websites. Such automatically collected information and data will not be disclosed save and except in accordance with the section entitled “Disclosure or Transfer of Data”. 

**Links to Other Sites**

The Websites may provide links to other websites which are not owned or controlled by the Publisher or its affiliates. Personal information and data from Users may be collected on these other websites when Users visit such websites and make use of the services provided therein. Where and when Users decide to click on any advertisement or hyperlink on the Site which grants Users access to another website, the protection of Users’ personal information and data which are deemed to be private and confidential may be exposed in these other websites. 

Non-registered Users who gain access to the Websites via their accounts in online social networking tools (including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter and Sina Weibo) are deemed to have consented to the terms of this Privacy Statement, and such Users' personal data which they have provided to those networking tools may be obtained by the Publisher and be used by the Publisher and its authorized persons in and outside of the User's country for the purpose of providing services and marketing materials to the Users. The Publisher and its authorised personnel may gain access and use the personal data of such Users so obtained, subject to the other provisions of this Privacy Statement. 

This Privacy Statement is only applicable to the Websites. Users are reminded that this Privacy Statement grants no protection to Users’ personal information and data that may be exposed on websites other than the Website, and the Publisher is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. Users are strongly recommended to refer to the privacy policies of such other websites before using those websites. 

**Security**

The security of Users’ personal information and data is important to the Publisher. The Publisher will always strive to ensure that Users’ personal information and data will be protected against unauthorised access. The Publisher has implemented appropriate electronic and managerial measures in order to safeguard, protect and secure Users’ personal information and data. 

All personal information and data provided by Users are only accessible by the authorised personnel of the Publisher or its authorised third parties, and such personnel shall be instructed to observe the terms of this Privacy Statement when accessing such personal information and data. Users may rest assured that their personal information and data will only be kept for as long as is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which it is collected. Registered User should safeguard his/her unique Username and Password by keeping it secret and confidential and never share these details with anyone. 

The Publisher follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information and data submitted by Users to the Websites, both during transmission and once the Publisher receives it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while the Publisher strives to protect Users’ personal information and data against unauthorised access, the Publisher cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**Retention of Personal Data**

Once the Publisher has obtained a User’s personal information and/or data, it will be maintained securely in the Publisher’s system for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes for which the data was collected as set out under the section headed “Purpose of Collection of Personal Data”. Once registered, Users may terminate his/her membership of the Website with the Publisher at whose contact details are set out under the section headed “Enquiries”. The Publisher may retain User’s personal information even after User’s has closed his/her account if retention is reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes between Users, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce this Privacy Statement and the Terms and Conditions. 

**Enquiries**

Should you have any enquiries relating to this Privacy Statement, please contact the Publisher via email at [helpdesk@headhunt.com.sg](mailto:helpdesk@headhunt.com.sg).
